The plane crash was just the beginning
Tape 407 is a horror, science fiction, thriller film directed by Dale Fabrigar.
Survivors of an airplane crash find themselves within the borders of
a government testing area and pursued by predators.
Trish, played by Abigail Schrader.
Jessie, played by Samantha Lester.
Jimmy, played by James Lyons.
Laura, played by Melanie Munt.
Lois, played by Samantha Sloyan.
Area 407 (originally titled Tape 407: The Mesa Reserve Incident) is a 2012 American found footage horror film directed by
Dale Fabrigar and Everette Wallin, starring Samantha Lester, James Lyons, Melanie Lyons and Abigail Schrader.
The film explores themes of dinosaur, airplane crash, found footage.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.